komli.net 2007-09-11

# Komli : Terms and Conditions

Please read this policy to understand what information Komli, Inc. (hereafter referred to as "Komli"), a Delaware Corporation, collects, how the information is used, and what choices you have regarding collection and use of your information when using Komli.

## Policy Scope

This policy covers information you share, both personally identifiable and non-identifiable information, with Komli as a visitor to the Komli web site. If you are a business using Komli's advertising network, then you are subject to the Komli Terms and Conditions. Please refer to the Komli Terms and Conditions for more information if this pertains to you.

## Information We Collect

Komli collects both personally identifiable information as well as non-personally identifiable information.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information is any information that identifies a specific individual, such as a name, email address, or phone number. 

To access Komli's ad network management capabilities, every user is required to provide a valid login and password. The login is assigned either by Komli or the customer's designated network administrator. Users of this site are typically employees or agents of our customers, and Komli employees. The login is associated with the user's personally identifiable information, consisting of his or her name, business email address, telephone numbers, and business address. 

Komli also collects personally-identifiable information in the following instances: 

  * A user voluntarily creates a user profile in the Linking area of the Komli web site. 

  * A user posts his or her email address in connection with providing comments to the Linking area of the Komli web site. 

  * A user enters the contact information for a business with which the customer transacts business using the Komli technology.

  * A user submits a comment or a query to our customer support staff.

Personally identifiable information may be transferred or used by technology service providers that Komli works with. These providers require access to information in order to provide services to the user. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

The Komli web site collects non-personally identifiable information on the Komli web site in the following instances: 

  * _Log files_. The Komli web site collects information about users and stores it in log files maintained on Komli and 3rd party equipment. This information includes non-personally identifiable information that your browser automatically sends whenever you visit this site, including information about your web request, your IP address your browser type, browser language, date and time of the request. 

  * _Cookies_. A session cookie is a small text file that the Komli web site generates and temporarily stores in the memory of the user's computer during the login session. Each time a user logs on to the Komli web site, the site issues a session cookie. The session cookie is linked to your login and enables Komli or relevant 3rd parties to monitor the Komli web site for unauthorized usage. The Komli web site cookie information is not combined with information from any ad serving cookies. 

  * _Clear pixels_. Clear pixels (also called web beacons and one-by-one pixels) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are used to remember the pages or sections of a site that a user visits. The Komli web site can use clear pixels in order to analyze the performance and usefulness of this site. 

## Information Use

Komli uses the personally identifiable information you share with us to respond to your query, comment, or to verify your credentials for access to its ad management network. 

Komli also uses the personally-identifiable information you provide to respond to your inquiries and requests, and to keep accurate records concerning the services you are requesting through the Komli web site.

All information may be used for additional purposes, such as auditing, research, and development of additional web site capabilities or services.

Komli generally uses non-personally identifiable information in aggregated form to help us measure the web site's performance and effectiveness, and to improve its usefulness. 

## Information Sharing

Komli does not rent, share, or sell the personally identifiable information you share with us without your prior permission.

Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information may be shared with 3rd party providers, in aggregated or unaggregated fashion. Some or all of the features of Komli's ad network management services may be provided by 3rd parties. In order for you to use Komli's ad network management features, your information may need to be transferred to these 3rd parties. 

Please note that we may also share information in the event that we are asked to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law.

If and when we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Komli may transfer the information it collects to any successor in interest to Komli (such as a company that acquires Komli), or internally to one or more affiliates (such as a corporate subsidiary or parent).

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy

When you use the Komli web site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and Komli will have the right to use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy, you must immediately discontinue use of the Komli web site. Komli reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Komli web site after a change in the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of those changes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Komli at [support@komli.com](mailto:support@komli.com).
